[{"answer": "Well, you know, that's a question that a lot of people are asking.", "docId": "121031pmt", "aSentId": 33, "question": "What can you tell me about the subway, about power and about when New York will be back on its feet?", "qSentId": 32}, {"answer": "Well, let me put it to you like this.", "docId": "121031pmt", "aSentId": 68, "question": "How are these generators, both at NYU and Bellevue, the backup generators, why are they failing?", "qSentId": 67}, {"answer": "Well, the devastation in the southern parts of our state, you know, demand our attention, our compassion and our prayer.", "docId": "121031pmt", "aSentId": 112, "question": "How are things where you are?", "qSentId": 111}, {"answer": "You know, we -- yes, first of all, we are happy that it is open and there will be more and more activity.", "docId": "121031pmt", "aSentId": 128, "question": "And maybe fully reopened within the next day or so, do you think?", "qSentId": 127}, {"answer": "I was in my apartment on the west side of Manhattan here.", "docId": "121031pmt", "aSentId": 153, "question": "Where were you?", "qSentId": 152}, {"answer": "I was looking at that.", "docId": "121031pmt", "aSentId": 178, "question": "What is wrong with that?", "qSentId": 177}, {"answer": "Well, did I say they want to kill Ali Velshi but they -- yes, Ali -- when I saw that --", "docId": "121031pmt", "aSentId": 185, "question": "What did he do here?", "qSentId": 184}, {"answer": "Well, yes, but there's a lot of things you could do on CNN to save many lives.", "docId": "121031pmt", "aSentId": 193, "question": "If it saves one life, isn't it worth it?", "qSentId": 192}, {"answer": "It's just because there's so much going on.", "docId": "121031pmt", "aSentId": 210, "question": "Now why is that?", "qSentId": 209}, {"answer": "Well, I'm -- firstly, I'm not a cynic.", "docId": "121031pmt", "aSentId": 316, "question": "Did you buy it or is there a more cynical, political reasoning behind what is going on?", "qSentId": 315}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "121031pmt", "aSentId": 329, "question": "Like this (INAUDIBLE), whichever way you dress this up, divorcing it from the storm, this cannot help Mitt Romney can it?", "qSentId": 328}, {"answer": "First of all, I don't think it's about Mitt Romney not being able to get on television.", "docId": "121031pmt", "aSentId": 364, "question": "But you could say by next Tuesday, if there are million so people still without power, feeling angry, you could get a protest vote, couldn't you?", "qSentId": 363}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, let's be clear.", "docId": "121031pmt", "aSentId": 385, "question": "How could this happen?", "qSentId": 384}, {"answer": "It is very easy to make that judgement from a ring side seat.", "docId": "121031pmt", "aSentId": 436, "question": "That is part of your job, isn't it?", "qSentId": 435}, {"answer": "You make valid points.", "docId": "121031pmt", "aSentId": 443, "question": "Michael, what do you think of this?", "qSentId": 442}, {"answer": "I will answer the way that Mayor Bloomberg answered this afternoon.", "docId": "121031pmt", "aSentId": 498, "question": "Could it be that?", "qSentId": 497}, {"answer": "It is the prime suspect.", "docId": "121031pmt", "aSentId": 511, "question": "From a meteorological point of view, is there any other explanation?", "qSentId": 510}, {"answer": "Absolutely, absolutely.", "docId": "121031pmt", "aSentId": 546, "question": "Do you believe the science is now incontrovertible?", "qSentId": 545}, {"answer": "These are the same people that say that Adam and Eve road on dinosaurs 6,000 years ago.", "docId": "121031pmt", "aSentId": 548, "question": "And when you hear mainly Republicans, it must be said, say the science is just a load of bunk, what do you say to them?", "qSentId": 547}, {"answer": "Well, Piers, the news is much more encouraging today than when I talked to you last night because what we have found is this, the National Guard has arrived, 45 members of the National Guard with 18 vehicles.", "docId": "121031pmt", "aSentId": 569, "question": "Is that what you are hearing?", "qSentId": 568}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "121031pmt", "aSentId": 591, "question": "But when these things happen, it really is inspiring to see how people react, isn't it?", "qSentId": 590}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "121031pmt", "aSentId": 595, "question": "Was that his name?", "qSentId": 594}, {"answer": "Well, they weren't prepared, but only in the sense that they haven't accepted that we are going to have more and more of this because of the climate change.", "docId": "121031pmt", "aSentId": 610, "question": "Were they prepared enough for this?", "qSentId": 609}]